{
	"Heavy Weather Changes": [
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle adjust its driving in snowy conditions?",
			"answers": [" Increase speed to reduce travel time.", "Activate snow mode, reduce speed, and increase following distance", "Turn off all automated systems and allow manual control.",
			 "Stop driving until the snow clears."],
			"correctAnswer": "Activate snow mode, reduce speed, and increase following distance."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when it encounters dense fog?",
			"answers": ["Speed up to get out of the fog quickly.", "Reduce speed, activate fog lights, and rely on radar and LIDAR sensors.",
			 "Turn on high beams and continue at normal speed.", " Stop immediately and wait for the fog to clear."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, activate fog lights, and rely on radar and LIDAR sensors."
		},
		{
			"question": "In case of heavy hail, what is the best course of action for an autonomous vehicle?",
			"answers": [
				"Continue driving as normal.",
				"Pull over to a safe location and wait for the hail to stop.",
				" Increase speed to avoid hail damage.",
				"Turn off all automated systems."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Pull over to a safe location and wait for the hail to stop."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle driving during a thunderstorm?",
			"answers": ["Maintain normal speed and ignore weather conditions.", "Reduce speed, ensure headlights are on, and be prepared for sudden stops.", "Stop driving and wait for the thunderstorm to pass.", "Rely solely on manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, ensure headlights are on, and be prepared for sudden stops."
		},
		{
			"question": "What adjustments should an autonomous vehicle make when driving through high winds?",
			"answers": [
				"Maintain normal speed and direction.",
				"Reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and stay alert for debris.",
				"Speed up to pass through the windy area quickly.",
				"Pull over and wait for the winds to die down."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and stay alert for debris."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle adjust its driving in heavy rain?",
			"answers": ["Maintain normal speed and rely on sensors.", 
			"Reduce speed, use wipers, and increase following distance.", 
			"Turn off automated systems and switch to manual control.", "Stop driving until the rain stops."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, use wipers, and increase following distance."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when it encounters black ice on the road?",
			"answers": [
				"Speed up to pass over the ice quickly.",
				"Reduce speed gradually, avoid sudden maneuvers, and alert other vehicles.",
				"Turn off all automated systems.",
				"Stop immediately and wait for the ice to melt."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed gradually, avoid sudden maneuvers, and alert other vehicles."
		},
		{
			"question": "In case of a dust storm, how should an autonomous vehicle respond?",
			"answers": ["Increase speed to get through the storm quickly.", "Reduce speed, use air filtration systems, and rely on radar sensors.",
			 "Continue driving at normal speed.", "Stop driving and wait for the storm to pass."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, use air filtration systems, and rely on radar sensors."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle driving during a heatwave?",
			"answers": [
				" Increase speed to keep the vehicle cool.",
				"Ensure the air conditioning system is on and monitor engine temperature.",
				"Drive only at night.",
				"Turn off all automated systems."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Ensure the air conditioning system is on and monitor engine temperature."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when it encounters a sudden hailstorm?",
			"answers": [
				"Speed up to avoid hail damage.",
				"Pull over to a safe location and wait for the hailstorm to pass.",
				" Ignore the hail and continue driving.",
				"Turn off all automated systems."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Pull over to a safe location and wait for the hailstorm to pass."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle driving through a flooded area?",
			"answers": ["Speed up to create a wave and pass through quickly.", 
			"Avoid the flooded area and find an alternative route.", "Continue driving at normal speed.", "Turn off all automated systems and switch to manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Avoid the flooded area and find an alternative route."
		},
		{
			"question": "What adjustments should an autonomous vehicle make when driving through strong crosswinds?",
			"answers": ["Maintain normal speed and direction.", "Reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and stay alert for sudden gusts.",
			 "Speed up to pass through the windy area quickly.", "Pull over and wait for the winds to die down."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and stay alert for sudden gusts."
		},
		{
			"question": "In case of a sudden temperature drop, how should an autonomous vehicle respond?",
			"answers": ["Speed up to reach the destination quickly.",
			 "Monitor tire pressure, adjust speed, and use anti-freeze systems.", "Turn off all automated systems and switch to manual control.",
			  "Stop driving until the temperature rises."],
			"correctAnswer": "Monitor tire pressure, adjust speed, and use anti-freeze systems."
		}
	],
	"Unexpected Road Obstacles": [
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when it detects a large pothole on the road?",
			"answers": ["Speed up to jump over the pothole.", "Slow down, navigate around it if possible, and notify other vehicles.",
			 "Ignore the pothole and continue driving.", "Stop immediately and wait for assistance."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, navigate around it if possible, and notify other vehicles."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to a sudden pedestrian crossing the road?",
			"answers": ["Honk the horn and continue driving.", "Slow down and stop if necessary to allow the pedestrian to cross safely.", "Speed up to pass before the pedestrian crosses.",
			 "Swerve around the pedestrian without reducing speed."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down and stop if necessary to allow the pedestrian to cross safely."
		},
		{
			"question": "When encountering debris on the highway, what should an autonomous vehicle do?",
			"answers": [
				"Drive over the debris without slowing down.",
				"Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the debris.",
				"Stop immediately and wait for the debris to be cleared.",
				"Increase speed to avoid the debris quickly."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the debris."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle a sudden tire blowout?",
			"answers": [" Immediately stop the vehicle.", "Gradually reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and safely pull over.", 
			"Continue driving at the same speed.", "Increase speed to maintain control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Gradually reduce speed, stabilize the vehicle, and safely pull over."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the appropriate response of an autonomous vehicle to an animal crossing the road?",
			"answers": [" Ignore the animal and continue driving.", "Slow down, sound the horn, and stop if necessary to avoid a collision.", 
			"Speed up to pass before the animal crosses.", "Swerve around the animal without reducing speed."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, sound the horn, and stop if necessary to avoid a collision."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when it detects a fallen tree on the road?",
			"answers": [
				"Drive over the tree without slowing down.",
				"Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the tree if possible",
				"Ignore the tree and continue driving.",
				"Stop immediately and wait for the tree to be removed."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the tree if possible"
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to a road construction site?",
			"answers": ["Maintain normal speed and ignore the construction.",
			 "Slow down, follow detour signs, and ensure safe navigation around the site.", "Speed up to pass through the construction quickly.",
			  "Stop and wait for the construction to be completed."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, follow detour signs, and ensure safe navigation around the site."
		},
		{
			"question": "When encountering a broken-down vehicle on the highway, what should an autonomous vehicle do?",
			"answers": [
				"Continue driving without slowing down.",
				"Alert other vehicles, reduce speed, and safely navigate around the broken-down vehicle.",
				"Stop immediately and wait for the broken-down vehicle to be towed.",
				"Increase speed to avoid the broken-down vehicle quickly."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Alert other vehicles, reduce speed, and safely navigate around the broken-down vehicle."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle a large pothole that suddenly appears?",
			"answers": ["Drive over the pothole without slowing down.", "Slow down, alert other vehicles, and safely navigate around the pothole.",
			 " Ignore the pothole and continue driving.", "Stop immediately and wait for the pothole to be filled."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, alert other vehicles, and safely navigate around the pothole."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the appropriate response of an autonomous vehicle to a fallen signpost on the road?",
			"answers": [
				"Ignore the signpost and continue driving.",
				"Slow down, alert other vehicles, and navigate around the signpost safely.",
				"Speed up to avoid the signpost quickly.",
				"Stop immediately and wait for the signpost to be removed."
			],
			"correctAnswer": " Slow down, alert other vehicles, and navigate around the signpost safely."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to sudden tire debris on the highway?",
			"answers": ["Drive over the debris without slowing down.", 
			"Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the debris safely.", " Ignore the debris and continue driving.",
			 "Stop immediately and wait for the debris to be cleared."],
			"correctAnswer": "Alert other vehicles, slow down, and navigate around the debris safely."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when encountering a pedestrian crossing the highway?",
			"answers": ["Honk the horn and continue driving.", "Slow down, stop if necessary, and allow the pedestrian to cross safely.",
			 "Speed up to pass before the pedestrian crosses.", "Swerve around the pedestrian without reducing speed."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, stop if necessary, and allow the pedestrian to cross safely."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle an unexpected cyclist on the road?",
			"answers": ["Ignore the cyclist and continue driving.", "Slow down, give the cyclist ample space, and pass safely.",
			 "Speed up to pass the cyclist quickly.", "Stop and wait for the cyclist to move aside."],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, give the cyclist ample space, and pass safely."
		}
	],
	"Heavy Traffic": [
		{
			"question": "In heavy traffic, how should an autonomous vehicle manage lane changes?",
			"answers": ["Change lanes frequently to find the fastest route.", 
			"Avoid changing lanes unnecessarily and maintain a safe distance.",
			 "Increase speed to merge quickly.",
			  "Turn off all automated systems and allow manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Avoid changing lanes unnecessarily and maintain a safe distance."
		},
		{
			"question": "What strategy should an autonomous vehicle use to navigate through a traffic jam?",
			"answers": ["Follow the vehicle in front closely to avoid losing space.", 
			"Maintain a safe following distance and avoid aggressive maneuvers.", "Constantly switch lanes to find a faster route.", 
			"Stop and wait for the traffic to clear."],
			"correctAnswer": "Maintain a safe following distance and avoid aggressive maneuvers."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to stop-and-go traffic?",
			"answers": ["Maintain a steady speed regardless of traffic conditions.", 
			"Adjust speed to match traffic flow and ensure smooth acceleration and deceleration.",
			 "Stop completely and wait for traffic to clear.", "Speed up to pass through the traffic quickly."],
			"correctAnswer": "Adjust speed to match traffic flow and ensure smooth acceleration and deceleration."
		},
		{
			"question": "In bumper-to-bumper traffic, what should an autonomous vehicle prioritize?",
			"answers": ["Aggressively changing lanes to find a faster route.", 
			"Keeping a safe following distance and preventing collisions.", " Speeding up to clear the traffic quickly.",
			 "Turning off all automated systems and relying on manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Keeping a safe following distance and preventing collisions."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle merging onto a busy highway?",
			"answers": ["Merge at a high speed to avoid slowing down other vehicles.",
			 "Use sensors to find a safe gap and merge smoothly at the appropriate speed.", 
			 "Stop at the merging point and wait for a clear road.", "Turn off automated systems and merge manually."],
			"correctAnswer": "Use sensors to find a safe gap and merge smoothly at the appropriate speed."
		},
		{
			"question": "In heavy traffic, how should an autonomous vehicle manage stop-and-go situations?",
			"answers": ["Maintain a steady speed regardless of traffic conditions.", "Adjust speed to match traffic flow and ensure smooth acceleration and deceleration.",
			 "Stop completely and wait for traffic to clear.", "Speed up to pass through the traffic quickly."],
			"correctAnswer": "Adjust speed to match traffic flow and ensure smooth acceleration and deceleration."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle merging in heavy traffic?",
			"answers": ["Merge at a high speed to avoid slowing down other vehicles.", "Use sensors to find a safe gap and merge smoothly at the appropriate speed.",
			 "Stop at the merging point and wait for a clear road.", "Turn off automated systems and merge manually."],
			"correctAnswer": "Use sensors to find a safe gap and merge smoothly at the appropriate speed."
		},
		{
			"question": "What strategy should an autonomous vehicle use to navigate through a congested intersection?",
			"answers": ["Aggressively change lanes to find the fastest route.", "Increase speed to clear the intersection quickly.",
			 "Wait patiently, follow traffic signals, and avoid unnecessary lane changes.", "Stop and wait for the intersection to clear."],
			"correctAnswer": "Wait patiently, follow traffic signals, and avoid unnecessary lane changes."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to slow-moving traffic?",
			"answers": ["Maintain normal speed and try to overtake other vehicles.",
			 "Adjust speed to match the flow of traffic and maintain a safe following distance.", "Stop completely and wait for traffic to clear.",
			  "Turn off automated systems and rely on manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Adjust speed to match the flow of traffic and maintain a safe following distance."
		},
		{
			"question": "In bumper-to-bumper traffic, what should an autonomous vehicle prioritize?",
			"answers": [
				" Speeding up to clear the traffic quickly.",
				"Turning off all automated systems and relying on manual control.",
				"Keeping a safe following distance and preventing collisions.",
				"Aggressively changing lanes to find a faster route."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Keeping a safe following distance and preventing collisions."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle manage lane changes in heavy traffic?",
			"answers": ["Turn off all automated systems and allow manual control.", "Change lanes frequently to find the fastest route.",
			 "Avoid changing lanes unnecessarily and maintain a safe distance.", "Increase speed to merge quickly."],
			"correctAnswer": "Avoid changing lanes unnecessarily and maintain a safe distance."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do when approaching a congested roundabout?",
			"answers": [
				"Slow down, yield to traffic, and enter the roundabout when safe.",
				"Stop at the entrance and wait for the roundabout to clear.",
				"Enter the roundabout quickly to avoid slowing down other vehicles.",
				"Turn off automated systems and rely on manual control."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Slow down, yield to traffic, and enter the roundabout when safe."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to a traffic jam on a freeway?",
			"answers": ["Speed up to find an opening in the traffic.", "Turn off all automated systems and switch to manual control.",
			 "Stop completely and wait for the traffic to clear.", "Reduce speed, follow the flow of traffic, and use navigation to find alternative routes if necessary."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed, follow the flow of traffic, and use navigation to find alternative routes if necessary."
		}
	],
	"Route Optimization": [
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle consider when optimizing a route?",
			"answers": ["Only the shortest distance.", "Traffic conditions, road closures, and weather forecasts.",
			 "Maximum speed limits on each road.", "Availability of scenic views."],
			"correctAnswer": "Traffic conditions, road closures, and weather forecasts."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle adjust its route in case of an unexpected road closure?",
			"answers": ["Turn off the automated system and find a new route manually.",
			 "Use real-time data to find the quickest alternative route.", "Stop and wait for the road to reopen.", 
			 "Continue towards the road closure and request manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Use real-time data to find the quickest alternative route."
		},
		{
			"question": "What factor is least important for an autonomous vehicle when planning a route?",
			"answers": [
				"Current weather conditions.",
				"Presence of toll roads.",
				"Shortest possible distance",
				"User's preferred driving speed."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "User's preferred driving speed."
		},
		{
			"question": "How does an autonomous vehicle use historical traffic data for route optimization?",
			"answers": ["To predict future traffic patterns and avoid congested areas.", "To find the most scenic route.",
			 "To ensure the vehicle always takes the same route.", "To calculate the shortest distance only."],
			"correctAnswer": "To predict future traffic patterns and avoid congested areas."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do if it encounters a high traffic area while following a pre-planned route?",
			"answers": ["Stick to the pre-planned route regardless of traffic.", 
			"Use alternative routes suggested by real-time traffic data.", "Stop and wait for traffic to clear.", "Switch to manual control."],
			"correctAnswer": "Use alternative routes suggested by real-time traffic data."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary goal of route optimization in autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": ["To find the longest possible route.", "To minimize travel time and fuel consumption.",
			 "To avoid highways.", "To maximize the number of stops."],
			"correctAnswer": "To minimize travel time and fuel consumption."
		},
		{
			"question": "How do autonomous vehicles determine the most efficient route?",
			"answers": ["By randomly selecting a route.", "Using GPS, real-time traffic data, and predictive algorithms.",
			 "By avoiding all major roads.", "By following a fixed, pre-programmed route."],
			"correctAnswer": "Using GPS, real-time traffic data, and predictive algorithms."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do if it encounters unexpected road closures?",
			"answers": ["Recalculate the route using real-time data and find an alternative path.",
			 "Stop and wait for the road to reopen.", "Ignore the closure and continue driving.", "Turn off all automated systems."],
			"correctAnswer": "Recalculate the route using real-time data and find an alternative path."
		},
		{
			"question": "How can autonomous vehicles optimize routes to reduce fuel consumption?",
			"answers": [
				"By taking the longest route possible.",
				"By stopping frequently.",
				"By driving at high speeds constantly.",
				"By avoiding traffic congestion and using the most direct path."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "By avoiding traffic congestion and using the most direct path."
		},
		{
			"question": "What technology assists autonomous vehicles in route optimization?",
			"answers": ["Manual maps.", "Satellite TV.", "GPS, traffic monitoring systems, and artificial intelligence.", "FM radio."],
			"correctAnswer": "GPS, traffic monitoring systems, and artificial intelligence."
		},
		{
			"question": "When faced with multiple route options, what should an autonomous vehicle prioritize?",
			"answers": ["The route with the least amount of technology required.", "The route with the highest number of stops.", "The route that minimizes travel time and avoids congestion.", "The route with the most scenic views."],
			"correctAnswer": "The route that minimizes travel time and avoids congestion."
		},
		{
			"question": "How do autonomous vehicles handle changing traffic conditions?",
			"answers": ["By dynamically adjusting routes based on real-time traffic data.",
			 "By stopping and waiting for traffic conditions to improve.", "By turning off all automated systems.", " By ignoring them and sticking to the pre-planned route."],
			"correctAnswer": "By dynamically adjusting routes based on real-time traffic data."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a key advantage of route optimization for autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": [
				"Increased fuel consumption.",
				"More frequent stops.",
				"Less use of technology.",
				"Reduced travel time and lower operational costs."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduced travel time and lower operational costs."
		}
	],
	"Safety & regulations": [
		{
			"question": "What must an autonomous vehicle do to comply with local traffic laws?",
			"answers": ["Follow all speed limits and traffic signals.",
			 "Only avoid collisions.", "Drive at maximum speed limits at all times.", "Follow manual control instructions from passengers."],
			"correctAnswer": "Follow all speed limits and traffic signals."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle handle emergency vehicles on the road?",
			"answers": ["Ignore them and continue driving.", "Yield the right of way and pull over if necessary.", 
			" Speed up to clear the area quickly.", "Stop immediately in the middle of the road."],
			"correctAnswer": "Yield the right of way and pull over if necessary."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a critical requirement for autonomous vehicles to operate on public roads?",
			"answers": [
				"High fuel efficiency.",
				"Compliance with all safety regulations and obtaining necessary permits.",
				"Ability to drive at high speeds.",
				"Comfortable seating for passengers."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Compliance with all safety regulations and obtaining necessary permits."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to a red traffic light?",
			"answers": ["Slow down but continue through the intersection.", "Stop completely and wait for the light to turn green.", 
			"Speed up to cross before the light changes.", "Ignore the traffic light and follow the pre-planned route."],
			"correctAnswer": "Stop completely and wait for the light to turn green."
		},
		{
			"question": "What ethical consideration should be programmed into autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": ["Prioritizing the safety of the vehicle's occupants over pedestrians.",
			 "Avoiding all collisions, regardless of consequences.", "Making decisions that ensure the greatest overall safety for all involved.",
			  "Minimizing financial costs of repairs and maintenance."],
			"correctAnswer": "Making decisions that ensure the greatest overall safety for all involved."
		},
		{
			"question": "What safety feature is essential for autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": ["Manual steering wheel control.", " Cassette player.", "Advanced emergency braking systems.", "Sunroof"],
			"correctAnswer": "Advanced emergency braking systems."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should autonomous vehicles do to comply with local traffic laws?",
			"answers": ["Follow all traffic signals, signs, and speed limits.", "Ignore all traffic signs.", "Only follow traffic laws during the daytime.", "Drive at any speed they choose."],
			"correctAnswer": "Follow all traffic signals, signs, and speed limits."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should autonomous vehicles be programmed to handle school zones?",
			"answers": ["Reduce speed and increase awareness for crossing children.", "Ignore school zone speed limits.", "Speed up to avoid stopping.", "Drive at the same speed as other vehicles."],
			"correctAnswer": "Reduce speed and increase awareness for crossing children."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary concern of safety regulations for autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": ["Ensuring the safety of passengers, pedestrians, and other road users.", "Increasing the number of vehicles on the road. ",
			 "Reducing the cost of vehicle maintenance.", "Improving entertainment systems."],
			"correctAnswer": "Ensuring the safety of passengers, pedestrians, and other road users."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should autonomous vehicles do in case of a system malfunction?",
			"answers": ["Continue driving as usual.", " Speed up to reach the destination quickly.",
			 "Safely pull over and notify the driver or authorities.", "Ignore the malfunction and keep going."],
			"correctAnswer": "Safely pull over and notify the driver or authorities."
		},
		{
			"question": "How can autonomous vehicles ensure compliance with safety regulations?",
			"answers": [
				"By ignoring software updates.",
				"By avoiding all safety checks.",
				"By regularly updating software and adhering to regulatory standards.",
				"By only operating during certain hours."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "By regularly updating software and adhering to regulatory standards."
		},
		{
			"question": "What role do ethical considerations play in the programming of autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": [
				"None at all.",
				"Only focusing on reducing costs.",
				"Ensuring decisions are made to maximize overall safety and minimize harm",
				"Ignoring the safety of pedestrians."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Ensuring decisions are made to maximize overall safety and minimize harm"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a key regulatory requirement for autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": ["Having a built-in entertainment system.", "Avoiding regular maintenance.", "Ignoring local traffic laws.", "Ensuring robust cybersecurity measures to protect against hacking."],
			"correctAnswer": "Ensuring robust cybersecurity measures to protect against hacking."
		}
	],
	"Others": [
		{
			"question": "What technology is essential for autonomous vehicles to detect their surroundings?",
			"answers": [
				"Manual steering wheel control.",
				"LIDAR, radar, and cameras.",
				"High-speed internet connection.",
				"Satellite TV."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "LIDAR, radar, and cameras."
		},
		{
			"question": "How should an autonomous vehicle respond to a passenger emergency, like a medical issue?",
			"answers": [
				"Continue driving to the destination.",
				"Pull over safely and notify emergency services.",
				"Speed up to reach the nearest hospital.",
				"Ignore the emergency and follow the pre-planned route."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Pull over safely and notify emergency services."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a major benefit of autonomous vehicles for urban transportation?",
			"answers": [
				"Increased fuel consumption.",
				"Reduced traffic congestion and improved road safety.",
				"Higher maintenance costs.",
				"Increased noise pollution."
			],
			"correctAnswer": " Reduced traffic congestion and improved road safety"
		},
		{
			"question": "How can autonomous vehicles contribute to environmental sustainability?",
			"answers": [" By using more fossil fuels.",
			 "By optimizing routes for fuel efficiency and reducing emissions.", "By increasing travel time.",
			  "By requiring frequent manual maintenance."],
			"correctAnswer": "By optimizing routes for fuel efficiency and reducing emissions."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should an autonomous vehicle do if it loses GPS signal during a trip?",
			"answers": [
				"Stop immediately and wait for the signal to return.",
				"Use onboard maps and sensors to navigate until the signal is restored.",
				"Drive in circles until the signal returns.",
				"Switch to manual control."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Use onboard maps and sensors to navigate until the signal is restored."
		},
		{
			"question": "How do autonomous vehicles benefit urban transportation systems?",
			"answers": [
				"By increasing traffic congestion.",
				"By increasing noise pollution",
				"By reducing traffic congestion and improving road safety.",
				"By using more fossil fuels."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "By reducing traffic congestion and improving road safety."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is an important consideration for autonomous vehicle manufacturers?",
			"answers": [
				"Ensuring vehicles are affordable and environmentally friendly.",
				"Reducing safety features.",
				"Increasing vehicle weight.",
				"Ignoring environmental impact."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Ensuring vehicles are affordable and environmentally friendly."
		},
		{
			"question": "How do autonomous vehicles impact the job market?",
			"answers": ["By creating more jobs for traditional drivers.", "By not affecting the job market at all.", "By eliminating all jobs in the transportation sector.", " By potentially reducing the need for certain driving jobs while creating new tech-related jobs."],
			"correctAnswer": " By potentially reducing the need for certain driving jobs while creating new tech-related jobs."
		},
		{
			"question": "What role do passengers play in autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": [
				"They must drive the vehicle manually.",
				"They have no role at all.",
				"They can take over control if needed and ensure safety.",
				"They must program the vehicle's route."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "They can take over control if needed and ensure safety"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a common misconception about autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": [
				"They require ongoing monitoring and updates to maintain safety and efficiency.",
				"They are completely error-free.",
				"They are the only solution for future transportation.",
				"They do not need any form of regulation."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "They require ongoing monitoring and updates to maintain safety and efficiency."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is a potential benefit of autonomous vehicles for elderly or disabled individuals?",
			"answers": ["Increased independence and mobility.", "Increased need for manual driving assistance.", "Higher transportation costs."
			, "Limited access to transportation."],
			"correctAnswer": "Increased independence and mobility."
		},
		{
			"question": "What infrastructure is important for the successful integration of autonomous vehicles?",
			"answers": [
				"Smart infrastructure with sensors and communication systems.",
				"More stop signs and traffic lights.",
				"Standard roads with no changes.",
				"Narrower roads."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Smart infrastructure with sensors and communication systems."
		},
		{
			"question": "What should autonomous vehicles do if they detect a potential collision?",
			"answers": [
				"Apply emergency brakes, alert the driver, and take evasive action if necessary.",
				" Speed up to avoid the collision.",
				"Continue driving at normal speed.",
				"Ignore the potential collision."
			],
			"correctAnswer": "Apply emergency brakes, alert the driver, and take evasive action if necessary."
		}
	]
}
